{
    "subject": "resource/The_Catskills_(painting)",
    "predicate": "ontology/museum",
    "object": "resource/Walters_Art_Museum",
    "human_readable": "The Catskills painting is held by Walters Art Museum.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9662559628486633,
            "question": "Are there other paintings by the same artist as 'The Catskills' in the Walters Art Museum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9109567403793335,
            "question": "Does the Walters Art Museum have a website where more information about 'The Catskills' can be found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962835073471069,
            "question": "What museum owns 'The Catskills' painting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8117885589599609,
            "question": "Are there any known exhibitions featuring 'The Catskills' painting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8061594367027283,
            "question": "Who painted 'The Catskills'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7650272250175476,
            "question": "What kind of artwork is 'The Catskills'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7213743329048157,
            "question": "Where is the painting 'The Catskills' located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.702056348323822,
            "question": "Is there any information about the artist of 'The Catskills' painting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6925885081291199,
            "question": "Is there any information about the subject of 'The Catskills' painting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5571790337562561,
            "question": "What year was 'The Catskills' painted?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Catskills painting is held by Walters Art Museum.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6840_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about the subject of 'The Catskills' painting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6840_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about the artist of 'The Catskills' painting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6840_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the painting 'The Catskills' located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6840_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6840_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context information, specifically from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6840/re-ranker-msmarco/136.txt, it is mentioned that \"The painting is owned by Walters Art Museum - Baltimore, and is accessible to the general public.\" This confirms that The Catskills painting is indeed held by the Walters Art Museum."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in `136.txt`, which states that \"The painting is owned by Walters Art Museum - Baltimore.\" This supports the query that The Catskills painting is held by Walters Art Museum."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}